<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arvind Kamal</title>
    <description>Arvind Kamal</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 18:05:20 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 18:05:20 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lunatic Who Shaped English</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;During a recent dive into history, I had the uncanny experience of crossing paths with the remarkable &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Chester_Minor&quot;&gt;Dr. William Chester Minor&lt;/a&gt;. At first glance, Dr. Minor seemed like a man of great stature - a skilled surgeon, a war veteran, and an avid bibliophile. But there was more to him than what met the eye - he was also a libertine, a schizophrenic, and, most infamously… a murderer. And yet, from within the walls of a mental asylum, he became one of the most vital contributors to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oed.com/?tl=true&quot;&gt;Oxford English Dictionary&lt;/a&gt;. This is the story of my encounter...</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-lunatic-who-shaped-english/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-lunatic-who-shaped-english/</guid>
        
        <category>book-review</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts To Text</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ever had an idea sit in the back of your mind for so long it practically gathered dust? That was me with blogging - something I’d toyed with for years but never acted on. Then, during a train ride, while chatting with my friend, Taylor (a seasoned blogger herself), about life beyond work, the topic came up. I mentioned my ever-growing backlog of ideas with nowhere to put them. Taylor, ever the enabler of creative pursuits, casually asked, “So why not start a blog? As someone who’s been blogging for years, I can tell you - you’re already doing the...</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 23:29:14 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/thoughts-to-text/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/thoughts-to-text/</guid>
        
        <category>musings</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
